Jilla Naithika

I completed my B.tech. I worked as a software engineer in ACCENTURE above 2.5 years.

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: +91-8465943867

Email: naithikajilla@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

• Total Experience 2 Years 10 Months

• Current Location Hyderabad/Secunderabad

Date of Birth Jun 13, 1999Gender Female

• Marital Status Single / Unmarried

SKILLS

- ASP.NET
- Azure Devops
- SQL

LANGUAGES KNOWN

- Telugu
- English
- Hindi

PROFILE SUMMARY

I worked as a application development analyst with 2.5 years of experience in azure devops. I am interested in automation testing and Azure devops technology and also interested in HR Recruiter and looking for new opportunities which suits me.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Graduation

Course B.Tech/B.E.(Computers)
College J.B. Institute of Engineering &

Technology, Hyderabad Year of Passing 2019 Grade 73%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 to Nov 2022

Application Development Analyst at Accenture

Jan 2020 to Nov 2022

Application Development Analyst at Accenture

Software Engineer

Jan 2020 to Nov 2022

Application Development Analyst at Accenture